nowloading.co 2016-12-29

# Privacy Policy — moviepilot.com

**Pay attention! This is our Privacy Policy. It matters because your privacy matters. This is where we explain how we collect and use information about you when you visit moviepilot.com and the related services available through our website (the “Site”).**

### Summary

The following bullet-points summarize some of the key information in this Privacy Policy. You can get more information under the “Full Privacy Policy” heading below. 

  * We call information that identifies you or that can be readily used to identify you (like name, address, email address, phone number, username, password, and other information you provide in posts) your “Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII.”   

  * We collect PII when you provide it, for example, by creating an account, logging in, submitting a request to the Site, or posting a review. Our main goals, in using this information, include to provide services to you and to maintain our Site.   

  * Keep in mind that your posts, comments, reviews or other content that you submit to the newsfeeds, blog, message board, microsites or any other part of the Site may be public and viewed by others. This means you have no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in the information you post to these forums on our Site – you got that, right? We want you to be safe, so be careful about what information you share.   

  * In fact, we might share the posts you make on our Site that can be seen by others with our business partners, including third-party websites who may re-publish the content on their own sites, including posts that may identify you.   

  * Otherwise, we share your PII with others only in limited circumstances. For example, if you log in to our Site through Facebook, some of your PII may be sent to us from them, or to them from us. Of course, we also share PII with service providers who help us run our business, pursuant to legal process (such as a government subpoena), and for other similar reasons.   

  * If you create an account or log in to our Site through Facebook or other social media, the information these third-party websites collect is subject to their own privacy policies, which you should read. You should also know we don't endorse, control, or have responsibility over the privacy practices of third-party websites, including those whose links are on our Site.  

  * We call information that the Site automatically collects that doesn’t readily identify you (like your IP address or operating system) “Non-Personally Identifiable Information.” The Site gathers information such as how you come to the Site and what you visit at the Site so we can understand how many visitors we have, when we receive the most visits, and for what content, much like television ratings that tell you how many people tuned in to a program.

  * We use "Cookies," which are pieces of information the Site stores on your computer, and similar technologies like “web beacons,” to record your preferences and information about your visit that helps us improve the Site. We also use these technologies to help tailor advertising to you, either on the Site or third-party websites. You can set your browser to refuse Cookies, but it may make the Site harder to use.   

  * You have options! For example, when you visit the Site, some ads may appear from third-party Internet advertising companies, which have their own privacy policies. You should read our “Full Privacy Policy” below to learn more about opting out of these ads. You can also choose to stop receiving marketing emails from Moviepilot by contacting us at feedback@moviepilot.com or using an opt-out tool included in our marketing emails.   

  * We work to protect your privacy but want you to know that no Internet transmission is totally secure. Be careful out there, and don't share sensitive information.   

  * Regarding children, our Site is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 and will delete it if we learn about it. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at privacy@moviepilot.com.   

  * If you create an account with the Site from outside the US, you should know that your information may be processed in the US where privacy regulations may be different from those of your home country. And if you live in California, you may have extra privacy rights.  

  * We may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. So you should keep checking back, but we'll let you know of any big changes.  

  * Email us at privacy@moviepilot.com with any questions, concerns, or comments about privacy on Moviepilot.  

### Full Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy below contains important and more detailed information regarding Moviepilot’s privacy practices and your choices. You should read this carefully before you use our Site. 

Moviepilot Inc. (“Moviepilot”) respects the privacy of visitors to its website moviepilot.com (the “Site”), which launched October 24, 2011. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains our information practices regarding the collection and use of your PII and other information collected when you use the Site.

The terms and conditions governing your use of the Site are contained in a separate Terms of Service agreement available here.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Moviepilot reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates. We will notify you of material changes to this privacy policy by posting the revised policy with the date it was revised on this page. Your continued use of our Site constitutes your agreement to this Policy and any updates. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to stay informed about how we are using the information we collect through the Site.

### Information We Collect

### Personally Identifiable Information

PII is information, such as your name, physical address, email address, cell phone number, other telephone numbers, password, username, gender, age, and other information, when it is linked to you or can be used to identify you. We collect PII when you voluntarily provide it or make it available to us by (1) logging into, or creating an account on our Site; (2) providing feedback to us through a feedback tool; (3) posting a review or making other comments on any public forums (“interactive features”) available on the Site; (4) entering a contest or sweepstakes or filling out a survey; or (5) logging in to our Site through a social media or similar tool. Each manner in which we collect PII about you identified above occurs only when you voluntarily provide information to us.

We also may monitor individuals’ activities on the Site such as the content they visit and the actions they take. We do this to understand our visitors’ preferences to help us improve Site performance, content selection, product design, and usability.

Regarding any public forums we may offer on our Site such as newsfeeds, blogs, message boards or similar tools (“interactive features”), the posts or comments you make may be public and viewed by others so you should use care before posting information about yourself, including PII, online. You acknowledge and understand that you have no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in the content you submit to interactive features over the Site. We assume no obligation to remove PII from postings on our Site and you disclose any PII in your postings at your own risk.

Regarding your creating an account or logging into our Site through a social media service or similar tool, such as Log in with Facebook or Sign in with Twitter (whether the use of such tools to sign in is optional or mandatory), any information that these third-party social media sites collect as a function of your using those sign-in tools is subject to those respective entities’ own privacy policies. If you sign in to our Site using such third-party sign-in tools, certain PII from those third-party websites or services will be shared with Moviepilot. We will treat this information shared with us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may combine the PII we collect from you with information we collect from other sources, both offline and online.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

The Site automatically also collects certain information that is not personally identifiable. For example, the Site automatically recognizes your domain name, IP address and region or geographical area, browser version, operating system and the website you passed through to reach our Site. In addition, our Site automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its various web pages or content, very much like television ratings that tell how many people tuned in to a program. We also may collect certain information through Cookies and similar tools as further described in the section below titled “Website Technology.” As noted above, we also may monitor identifiable individuals’ activities when they use the Site to help us improve Site performance, content selection, product design, and usability.

### Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We primarily use the PII we collect about you (1) to provide our Site and services to you; (2) to allow us to properly maintain our Site and our services and to make improvements or upgrades as we deem appropriate; (3) to send you newsletters about topics that we believe are of interest to you; (4) to inform you of products or services from us or others that may be of interest to you; (5) to respond to your inquiries; (6) to prevent fraud, including the unauthorized use of this Site or our services or violations of applicable policies and Terms of Service; and (7) to ensure our own compliance with the law. We may also use PII to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our agreements with you, including any website Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy.

### Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information

Except as otherwise described in this section, we do not share your PII with third parties for their own use. To respond to your requests or to process your information for any of the activities identified in the “Use of Personally Identifiable Information” section above, we may share your PII with our affiliates, business partners, or others who work for us, such as service providers, vendors, contractors, and agents. In addition, when you post any publicly-viewable information to interactive features (see the PII subsection under “Information We May Collect”), we may share your post with our business partners, including third-party websites who may re-publish such content, including posts that may identify you.

When you log-in to the Site through a social media (also referred to as social networking) service using tools like Log In With Facebook, we send the social networking service information about you, including information about your use of the services we offer on the Site. In addition, we or you may facilitate or be able to publish information about your activities on the Site on these third-party social media services. For example, your posts on our Site might also be shared and posted on your page at one of our partner social media service websites. Please note that when information about your activities on our Site is published on social networking services, that information will be visible to users of those services and will be handled in accordance with, and subject to, the privacy policies of those services. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with those services’ privacy policies and privacy controls. In addition, when you visit the Site while logged in to one of those services, the third-party social media service provider may be able to identify you and associate the technical information provided to your web browser with other information the service already has about you.

We may also share PII in the following circumstances: (1) upon receipt of a governmental request for information; (2) in response to a subpoena or a court order; (3) to comply with relevant laws; (4) in response to an investigation of fraud regarding a specific individual; (5) in an effort to safeguard the person or property of a Moviepilot employee or a third party; or (6) when we believe it is necessary to protect our interests, or we believe in good faith that the law requires the sharing of your PII.

In addition, Moviepilot may, in the future, decide to sell, merge or otherwise reorganize its business or assets. Moviepilot reserves the right to transfer and disclose PII in these circumstances to an entity acquiring the company or relevant assets.

Finally, we may also share de-identified aggregate information with third parties and advertisers so they can measure the effectiveness of any advertisements viewed in connection with the Site and understand their audiences. For example, we may tell advertisers the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement.

### Our Use of Website Technology (including Cookies)

We use PII which we aggregate with other users’ PII into a de-identified form, or non-personally identifiable information collected through website technologies to help us to tailor the features, performance and support of our products and services to Site users. The non-personally identifiable information we collect and data that we may aggregate in de-identified form may be shared with our affiliates and third parties to provide you with more relevant services and advertisements, including advertisements relating to the Site on other websites you may visit.

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that any website may transfer to your browser that are then stored in your computer’s system. We use Cookies to store users’ preferences and to record information about your visit to the Site. We also use Cookies to customize newsletter, advertising and web page content based on browser type and user profile information. The deposit of Cookies by the Site may enhance your online experience by allowing us to save your preferences for your next visit. Our Cookies may also measure the general activity on the Site and measure advertising effectiveness, which allows us to determine which areas and features are most popular. This information allows us to make improvements to our Site. Cookies may also help us to tailor advertising to you on the Site or on other websites, including with the assistance of third-party Internet advertising companies, described below.

Most web browsers are set up to accept Cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. If you choose to decline Cookies, some of the functionality of the Site may be impaired.

### Web Beacons and Pixel Tags

Web beacons, also known as “clear gifs”, “one-pixel gifs”, “web bugs”, “Internet tags” or “pixel tags”, are small graphic images (usually invisible) that can be embedded in content and advertising on a website or in an email. These may be embedded on the Site or on advertisements for Moviepilot appearing on third-party websites or in email. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on your browser, check whether you have viewed a web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date that you viewed the web beacon, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the web beacon was viewed. We use web beacons to improve your Moviepilot experience, including to provide you with content customized to your interests.

### Third-Party Ad Networks

Some of the advertisements that appear in connection with the Site may be delivered to you by third-party Internet advertising companies (also called “ad networks” or “network advertisers”). These companies may use Cookies, web beacons and other technologies, including those on our Site, to collect information about your use of the Site or third-party websites, to deliver advertisements to you, measure their effectiveness, and personalize advertising content. The information practices of these advertising companies are governed by their own privacy policies and are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Some of these advertising companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), a cooperative of online marketing companies that offers a centralized tool for opting out of behavioral advertising delivered by each of its member companies. If you would like to obtain more information about the NAI and make choices about their members’ use of your information, please click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed. Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different websites. To make choices about interest-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA consumer opt out page. See http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/[#completed](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed). 

### Links to Third-Party Websites

We may provide links to third-party websites. You acknowledge that such links are provided for your convenience only and do not constitute an endorsement by Moviepilot of such third-party websites. Since we do not control these third-party websites, we assume no responsibility for the privacy practices of such websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on those, and all, third-party websites.

### Protecting Your Information

Moviepilot employs reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the PII we collect online. However, Moviepilot does not warrant or represent that its level of security meets or exceeds any specific standards. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is 100% secure or error-free, nor is stored data free from vulnerabilities. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, the Site, or our services, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We are not responsible for the actions of third parties.

### Children’s Privacy

Our Site is directed towards adults. We do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have PII on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information.

### Your Choices

If at any subsequent time, you wish to stop receiving marketing communications from Moviepilot (e.g., by email), please change the respective settings in your profile on the Site or contact us at feedback@moviepilot.com to make this request.

### Non-U.S. Site Users

Please note that the Site is directed toward users who reside in the United States. If you create an account or log in to the Site from outside the United States, you will have agreed to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. Your PII and other information may, at our sole discretion, be transferred to and processed in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may be different than other parts of the world, such as the European Union and may not offer an equivalent level of protection to that in the European Union or certain other countries.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have provided PII to the Site to request certain information regarding Moviepilot’s disclosure of PII to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of PII disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of the third parties when required. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this section.

If you have any questions about your California privacy rights or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@moviepilot.com or in writing at:

Moviepilot, Inc.  
2100 Abbot Kinney | Unit D  
Venice Beach  
CA 90291  
USA

### How Can You Ask Questions or Raise Concerns?

If you have other questions or concerns about our privacy policies or data use, or wish to change your options, email us at privacy@moviepilot.com.

 _Effective Date: October 24, 2011; revised September 2013_
